Hey everyone, welcome to another video on my channel.
Maybe you have seen the sign on the thumbnail which said new brand,
so I'm going to introduce a new brand here today.
The brand itself is new, but it's the first time I'm going to show it to you here on my YouTube channel.
And today's set brand is Neophoric.
They make these graphic, dark, techwear, rave designs.
and I'm super happy I can show you these outfits because I think they're really
really awesome so before I'm going to tell you more about them I will get
changed and show the first one. So they call this kind of graphic wear
technical apparel and I think if you have a look at the print you can see why
it looks a bit like a PCB and I first wanted to show you the cut of the pants
here. I think they're really really flattering. They have this overlapping V shape here and the
jacket is also super cool with the long arms and the thumb holes here. So that is the first outfit.
I can also close this and I'm going to pimp it a bit.
added some boots and this belt back here and I think it's already cool
techwear inspired look so I would wear this to a goth party you can also wear it to a rave
or just as really cool everyday fashion they gained a lot of attention via social media
and you can see a lot of dark rave and techno DJs wearing that kind of outfits and their
brand so I think they have some really cool looks. They're located in San Diego, California. They also
have a showroom there and they designed special fabrics. They also have the screen printing
process which they do at their location in San Diego. I can already show you that this one is
more shiny for example whereas this one is more matte and they put a lot of
thought behind their designs and behind the process which I think it's also
really cool it's a really nice slow fashion brand I'm going to close this zipper so
it's high-necked I also really love the arrows here and the back prints almost
like a spine there are small pockets in the front which are actual pockets and
can put something inside like your hands or small items and it's really really
comfy so the fabric feels so high quality and smooth and stretchy and I
just love wearing it I do have a second outfit a bodysuit and some leg warmers
see you in a sec second outfit it's this bodysuit and the leg warmers they stay
ups. I'm wearing size medium in the bodysuit and I ordered the tall option so there are two
length options available which is really great and in comparison this fabric isn't as stretchy
as the fabric from the jacket for example. In the jacket I was wearing size small so if you
think about ordering bodysuit I recommend to size up and if you're tall like me then use the tall
option. Neo Floric does not only do black on black prints but you get also white or pink prints for
example and another feature of this bodysuit is this really really cool silver back print here.
I just love this design. My both heart beats fast for the black on black prints.
For this bodysuit because I think it is so awesome I'm going to show you two styling options
besides the classy fishnets and leg warmers and the first one is going to be
with the skirt. Alright I put a skirt on and I have a feeling that this is like a
bit too dressed so something I saw on the neophoric page online was that they
used this bodysuit even more as a top and they folded it inside.
So then it looks like a crop top.
Now I think that's a completely different look.
You can still see the tights.
I think that's a really cool version and really cool option to change up the bodysuit look
and just wear it like a top.
And for the last option I'm going to pair it with these pants.
Final outfit and I think this is also a really nice combination.
Just the classy leggings, actually this is the ultra leggings from Paradise and the shine
matches really well with the print from the bodysuit.
I could also add like a bag like this and this would be like a cool look to go shopping
into the city.
I don't know.
I'm definitely going to wear this out someday.
I really like it and yes I know that Nora really likes these shoes, well I do and I
I know a lot of other people do too.
They're really comfy.
They're really handy for partying.
And I don't think they look that bad.
That's my preference.
My personal one.
And if you don't like them, that's on you.
From the three outfit combinations, I think...
This one is my favorite.
Or maybe the first one with the fishnets and the leg warmers.
But I really like this look.
Maybe because I just am that.
kind of pants and bodysuit girl and
Yeah, I also really really like
The jacket from the beginning. I think this one had an awesome fit and material. So yeah
Totally can recommend this brand and since they put a lot of
Thought into their brand. I'm going to read out a few sentences for you from
neoforik
because I think they can say best what they want to tell with their clothing.
We're a futuristic clothing brand that creates high-quality, bold and expressive graphic wear designed to embody a mindset of
individuality and intentional focus on
electric topics. When a noise is gone, we can focus on enhancing ourselves to then enhance our environment and lift others up.
And with these words, I can only tell you to check out the shop I'll link in the description text and their socials.
I really like their aesthetic. I'm really happy that we could collaborate for this video. So thank you for these awesome clothes. And yeah, I hope you enjoyed this video. Tell me in the comments what was your favorite outfit. Also check out my Patreon and my other socials. And I will see you in the next video. Have a nice day. Bye.